{
    "id": "52851325aed64fb6b1790de3031cfca8",
    "title": "Personal Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "……………………… need help.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "Me"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It’s …………………………. that needs help.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "me",
                "you",
                "they"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "John has broken his leg. ........................................ will be in hospital for a few days.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "He",
                "Him",
                "His"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Tell Jane I miss .....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "she",
                "her",
                "he"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Jane and Alice are friends. ......................................... like each other very much.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "They",
                "Them",
                "She"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Who’s that over there?’ ‘.................................. is Peter Cook.’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "They",
                "She",
                "It"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Hello. .................................. is Alan Williams.’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "It",
                "He"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Mary is learning music. .......................................... has a golden voice.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "She",
                "Her"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "On Mary’s birthday, Alice gave ...................................... a watch.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "she",
                "her"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Harry is a brilliant student. ...................................... has won many prizes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "He",
                "Him",
                "They"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}